https://www.afsnet.org/privacy.aspx

American Folklore Society
HomeAbout AFS
About AFSLeadership and Governance
AFS BylawsAFS Board Meeting MinutesAFS FellowsAFS LeadershipAFS Life MembersAFS Long Range Plan
Projects
AFS Oral History ProjectJames Madison Carpenter CollectionChina-US Folklore and ICH ProjectConsultancy/Professional Development ProgramFolklore and Public Policy Working GroupsFolklore and Museum Policy Working GroupFolklore and Historic Preservation Working GroupInternational PartnershipsNational Folklore Archives InitiativeUNESCOVeterans History ProjectWIPO
Position Statements
CompensationEthics Human SubjectsPromotion and Tenure
Prizes
AFS Lifetime Scholarly Achievement AwardBenjamin A. Botkin PrizeChicago Folklore PrizeKenneth Goldstein Award
Archie Green AwardZora Neale Hurston PrizeJudith McCulloh AwardAmérico Paredes PrizeAFS Section Prizes
Privacy StatementContact AFS
Annual Meetings
2020 Annual MeetingFuture Annual MeetingsPast Annual MeetingsGeneral Annual Meeting Information
Membership
Join AFSMember Benefits and CategoriesMember Directory
Sections
About AFS SectionsSections ListSection PublicationsSection PrizesResources for Conveners
Publications
Journal of American FolkloreSection PublicationsReportsPublications about AFS and FolkloreWhy I'm a Folklorist
Resources
AFS ReviewCommunity CalendarCareer CenterThe Folklore WikiWhere to Study FolkloreOpen ForumsOpen Folklore
AFS Teaching Resources Bank
AFS Ethnographic ThesaurusFolklore Advocacy ToolkitReports from Professional Development ProjectNotable Folklorists of ColorCovid-19 ResourcesWebinars
Support AFS
Search »
Print Page   |   Contact Us   |   Your Cart   |   Sign In   |   Join AFS
Privacy Policy
Last updated: 1/23/2019
At the American Folklore Society (AFS), we are committed to protecting your privacy. We aim to collect only the information that is required to provide services to our members or event attendees. If you have any concerns or questions about data privacy, contact us at AmericanFolkoreSociety@gmail.com.
We are committed to on-going efforts to be explicit when we collect data about how it will be used, and to give you an opportunity to give or withhold consent.
AFS operates a website, http://afsnet.org, which is our primary system for: managing all data, including membership and event registration transactions, that are collected online; recording membership, event, store and donation transaction details, including those that are paid by cash or check (transaction details include the date, billing name and mailing address, amount and method of payment, and product details; they do not include credit card, account or routing information); and communicating with members. This website is a service provided by YourMembership; for more information about how YourMembership manages the data collected on our website, see https://unity.yourmembershipinc.com/privacy.aspx.
AFS uses BluePay to process all credit card payments that we receive. AFS can access the billing information, like name and address data, but not the credit card information associated with these transactions. For more information about how BluePay manages data privacy, see https://www.bluepay.com/privacy-policy/.
AFS uses services provided by Zoho to collect and manage annual meeting proposal data. For more information about how Zoho manages data privacy, see https://www.zoho.com/privacy.html.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date above and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at AmericanFolkoreSociety@gmail.com.
Sign In
Remember Me
Forgot your password?Haven't joined AFS yet?
moreCommunity Calendar
10/7/2020 » 10/9/2020Digital Truth Making: Online Conference10/10/2020 » 10/11/2020Traditional Tunes and Popular Airs: Exploring Musical Resemblance Conference10/11/2020World Storytelling Institute's Storytelling Workshops for Adults10/14/2020 » 10/17/20202020 Annual Meeting of the American Folklore Society
Career Center|Open Forums|Online Store|Renew|Member Search|Privacy Policy|Donate|Press RoomAmerican Folklore SocietyClassroom-Office Building, Indiana University, 800 East Third Street, Bloomington IN 47405 USA812/856-2379; www.afsnet.orgHeadquartered on the campus of Indiana University-Bloomington, AFS appreciates the generous support of the IU College of Arts and Sciences.
Association Management Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
